e-architect.co.uk 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy - e-architect

_World Buildings across the Globe, Cookies_

Website Information : Privacy Policy

## Website Privacy Policy

**Legal**

Please note that your use of this site is governed by the Legal Information available here and elsewhere on the site. By proceeding to access this site, you are deemed to have accepted those terms.

Last updated on 28 December 2015

You must read the following information before proceeding. It provides information on some of the laws and regulations applicable to this web site.

This site uses cookies – small text files that are placed on your machine to help the site provide a better user experience. In general, cookies are used to retain user preferences, store information for things like shopping carts, and provide anonymised tracking data to third party applications like Google Analytics. As a rule, cookies will make your browsing experience better. However, you may prefer to disable cookies on this site and on others. The most effective way to do this is to disable cookies in your browser. We suggest consulting the Help section of your browser or taking a look at [the About Cookies website](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) which offers guidance for all modern browsers

**Privacy Policy**

We take the privacy of our customers very seriously and we are concerned to protect your personal data. We believe it is important that you know how we treat the information about you that we receive through this web site. Therefore we will only use your personal information as set out in this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions in relation to the information we hold about you or our use of that information, please feel free to contact us.  
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
By enabling Google Analytics Advertising Features we enable Google Analytics to collect data about our traffic in addition to data collected through a standard Google Analytics implementation.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**Important Legal Information**

Personal Data  
In general, you may visit this web site without revealing any information about yourself. Our servers collect the numbers of visitors. This information is anonymous and we aggregate it to measure the use of our web site.

Adverts  
We host advertisements by a third party on the site. The third party may collect anonymous information about your visits to our web site. The third party may use information about your visits to this and other web sites. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by the third party please contact us.

Projects  
Once information has been submitted to us we retain the right to publish. Subsequent requests for removal of information will not be accepted as this contravenes our SEO policy. Unlinking of pages / information will be considered on a case by case basis.

**Further Information**

Please note that we may change this Privacy Policy or Important Legal Information from time to time so please check it regularly.  
This web site may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those other sites.

Skyscraper Buildings  
  
_image © AS+GG_

New House Designs  
  
_photograph : Peter Cook_

Frank Gehry  
  
_image from Saadiyat_

_photograph : Adrian Welch_

Comments for the _World Architecture Privacy Policy_ page welcome

Privacy Policy – page

No tags for this post.
